is this very smooth
exponential process
Just like in the
90s you saw Moore's
law that the amount
of power would double
every 12 months or
every 18 months We
have a Moore's law
like law except it's
for intelligence itself for
the cognitive ability of
the across many tasks
So what we are
seeing is that that
ability is
depending on how you
measure it every four
to 12 months So
we're just the of
cognitive ability and where
we are now is
to take coding as
one example that's been
exploding really fast over
the last year or
two I have engineers
in the team that
one of our lead
products Code which is
the way you use
our for coding
He says he hasn't
written any code in
the last two It's
all Claude He's edited
it he's looked at
it but it's all
been written by Indeed
we recently released this
thing called Cowork which
was Claude Code to
non coding tasks
It really seems to
have off wrote it
in like a week
and a almost entirely
with Claude Code